I can do it.
It was the most exciting day I think
I've ever done in my entire life. So, I
made a post yesterday just to like put
some feelers out there and see if
anybody would be interested in buying
the first skoolie that we converted.
There's been some clear interest. And
now I have to formulate a plan. I'm not
using it. I loved it. I loved that
little bus.
That was the bus that started it all.
That bus was my exit plan. Money isn't
the main concern. We want it to go to
the right people. The people that are
going to use it to find their space. So,
you're going to apply. Tell us your
story. Tell us who you are. What this
bus means to you. What you would be
doing with it. And then from there,
we'll select a couple applicants and
then open up like a
a raffle. Uh what's it called?
Auction. Then we'll do an auction
between the people that we pick out of
the application process that have great
stories and and vibes and
happiness and rainbows, kittens, and
unicorns, and stuff. Then the highest
bid from that group of people then wins.
And I think it'd be fun too if like we
we were able to do like a video series
to like show you guys the people that we
picked to to explain their story. Where
they came from. Where they're going. Why
they're doing this. What the story is. I
like people's stories. I'll release all
the details on the bus. What it is. It's
got badass engine. It's a manual. It's
just cute. It's just cute. I love that
bus. I love that bus and and it it for
me that bus
was like
I can do it. I can do it. It was the
most exciting thing I think I've ever
done in my entire life. It's a It's a
symbol of happiness, peace,
independence. It's a symbol of freedom
and and I love it. And I want somebody
else to love it as much as I loved it.
So, we're going to do application
process and then we're going to do a
little auction between the people we
choose and hopefully we'll be able to
kind of spin the story out to you guys
so you can see who these people are. And
oh or should we do like a people's
choice award? We could let the people
decide on who should get it.
I don't know. We'll figure it out.
Anyways, that's where we're going. Game
plan, bus. Woo!